<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nomad Massage</title><link>https://www.nomad-massage.com/</link><description>Recent content on Nomad Massage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-nz</language><atom:link href="https://www.nomad-massage.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.nomad-massage.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nomad-massage.com/about/</guid><description>Nomad Massage offers expert massage therapy, by a qualified therapist, in the comfort of your own home.
My name is Marine and I comes from France. With over 10 years experience behind me, I like to use a variety of techniques. I have a very intuitive approach to massage and enjoy when you let me “follow the flow”, finding the muscles that need the most focus and attention.
My ever growing knowledge on holistic well being is what I cherishes most, and likes to share.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.nomad-massage.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nomad-massage.com/contact/</guid><description>Mon to Fri : 3 pm - 6 pm Sat to Sun : 9 am 4 pm Phone : 021 037 1285
Email : marinemathieu1802@gmail.com
Halswell, Christchurch 8025</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://www.nomad-massage.com/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nomad-massage.com/faq/</guid><description>How do I make a booking? You can either send a text or an email with your preferred day and time, as well as the length of massage needed, and I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as possible.
How do I make payment? Payment can either be made through bank transfer or cash.
When am I expected to pay? You can pay by internet banking at the time of booking.</description></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://www.nomad-massage.com/pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nomad-massage.com/pricing/</guid><description> 60 min : $80 90 min : $110 Travel fee Halswell : free of charge South West of Christchurch : $10 Christchurch central and East : $20 Available only for a group (2 or more). The travel fee applies only once for the group.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://www.nomad-massage.com/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.nomad-massage.com/services/</guid><description>I offer a range of massage therapies, for chronic pain and to support your wellness, such as :
relaxation massage A light to medium pressure massage, for relaxing the body and mind.
deep tissue massage A firm pressure massage, including trigger points, to focus on specific tension and knots.
sports massage A tonic massage to give quick relief to sore muscle and prevent injuries.
pregnancy massage A gentle massage tailored to the needs of pregnancy aches and pain.</description></item></channel></rss>